Cos ah ah I’m in the stars tonight
-- 今夜我置身於星空
So watch me bring the fire and set the night alight
-- 看我用火花照亮這夜晚
Shoes on get up in the mornCup of milk let’s rock and roll
-- 清早起床 提鞋穿上 牛奶一杯 整装待發
King Kong kick the drum rolling on like a rolling stone
-- 金剛擊鼓 滾石一樣
Sing song when I’m walking home
-- 步行返家 沿路歌唱
Jump up to the top LeBron
-- 高高躍起 如勒布朗
Ding dong call me on my phone
-- 叮咚 给我電話
Ice tea and a game of ping pong
-- 冰红茶 加一局乒乓
This is getting heavy
-- 氣氛漸熱
Can you hear the bass boom, I’m ready
-- 聽見貝斯 我已就绪
Life is sweet as honey
-- 人生似糖如蜜
Yeah this beat cha ching like money
-- 這節奏珠光寶氣
Disco overload I’m into that I’m good to go
-- 迪斯科派对 很好我已就绪
I'm diamond you know I glow up
-- 我是鑽石 閃閃發光
Hey, so let’s go
-- 一起去吧
Cos ah ah I’m in the stars tonight
-- 今夜我置身于星空
So watch me bring the fire and set the night alight
-- 看我用火花照亮這夜晚
Shining through the city with a little funk and soul
-- 放克靈魂 閃耀全城
So I’mma light it up like dynamite, woah
-- 我像火光 讓它照亮
Bring a friend join the crowd
-- 叫上朋友 加入這里
Whoever wanna come along
-- 無論是谁 願者皆可
Word up talk the talk just move like we off the wall
-- 話不多说 盡情搖擺
Day or night the sky’s alight
-- 不分晝夜 天空明亮
So we dance to the break of dawn
-- 徹夜熱舞 直到黎明
Ladies and gentlemen,I got the medicine so you should keep ya eyes on the ball, huh
-- 女士先生 交付給我 專注現在
This is getting heavy
-- 氣氛漸熱
Can you hear the bass boom, I’m ready
-- 聽見貝斯 我已就绪
Life is sweet as honey
-- 人生似糖如蜜
Yeah this beat cha ching like money
-- 節奏珠光宝气
Disco overload I’m into that I’m good to go
-- 迪斯科派對 我已就绪
I'm diamond you know I glow up
-- 我是鑽石 閃閃發光
Let’s go
-- 一起去吧
Cos ah ah I’m in the stars tonight
-- 今夜我置身于星空
So watch me bring the fire and set the night alight
-- 看我用火花照亮这夜晚
Shining through the city with a little funk and soul
-- 放克靈魂 閃耀全城
So I’mma light it up like dynamite, woah
-- 我會像煙火照亮
Dynnnnnanana, life is dynamite
-- 人生如煙火
Shining through the city with a little funk and soul
-- 放克靈魂 閃耀全城
So I’mma light it up like dynamite, woah
-- 我會像煙火照亮
Dynnnnnanana eh
-- 煙火照亮
Light it up like dynamite
-- 像煙火般照亮
Dynnnnnanana eh
-- 煙火照亮
Light it up like dynamite
Cos ah ah I’m in the stars tonight
-- 今夜我置身于星空
So watch me bring the fire and set the night alight
-- 看我照亮夜空
Shining through the city with a little funk and soul
-- 放克靈魂 閃耀全城
So I’mma light it up like dynamite
-- 煙火照亮
Cos ah ah I’m in the stars tonight
-- 今夜我置身于星空
So watch me bring the fire and set the night alight
-- 看我照亮夜空
Shining through the city with a little funk and soul
-- 放克靈魂 閃耀全城
So I’mma light it up like dynamite, woah
-- 我會像煙火照亮
Dynnnnnanana, life is dynamite
-- 人生如煙火
Shining through the city with a little funk and soul
-- 放克靈魂 閃耀全城
So I’mma light it up like dynamite, woah
-- 煙火照亮
--